<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competition on Red Ambassador Music</title>
    <link>http://redambassadormusic.com/tags/competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Competition on Red Ambassador Music</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://redambassadormusic.com/tags/competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 LMMS Christmas Competition Winners</title>
      <link>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/2014-lmms-christmas-competition-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/2014-lmms-christmas-competition-results/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations to all of our winners! Thank you for participating in this year’s competition. It’s exciting to see all these LMMS artists coming together.
This year, we made ACTUAL AWARDS for 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners! Yes, they’re paper/pdf awards, but better than nothing, eh? Maybe you can print them off and put them on your wall or take a picture of you holding your award and post it to my Facebook page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS!! – Spade’s in a Remix Contest</title>
      <link>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/spade-in-a-remix-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/spade-in-a-remix-contest/</guid>
      <description>So, I just wanted to give a shout out to a musical bro of mine. He just submitted his remix entry to the Citizen’s “Made Alive” remix contest. I was chatting with Spade and he was saying how excited he was to enter into this contest and I think that excitement really shows in the product that came out.
You gotta listen to his remix of Citizen’s song “Made Alive”! 😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 LMMS Christmas Competition Winners</title>
      <link>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/2013-lmms-christmas-competition-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://redambassadormusic.com/blog/2013-lmms-christmas-competition-results/</guid>
      <description>Hey everybody!
Spade and I would both like to sincerely thank you for participating in the 2013 Top-10 LMMS Christmas Music competition. We hope you all had fun and were able to get valuable feedback from us and your peers.
Here are the tracks that made it into the top ten list.
Again: Congratulations and Merry Christmas!
List of 2013&amp;rsquo;s Top-10 LCC Entries    # Artist Track Title     1 Forward Notion O Come O Come Emmanuel   2 RoboP LMMS 2013   3 Raptor980 Music God Rest Ye Marry Gentlemen   4 Nathan (Tripliex) Jingle Bells – 2013   5 Sti-Jay Calm Christmas   6 FaZz-2 BumpinBells   7 Ronald Hutasuhut Sukacita (Joyful)   8 Stakeout Punch Broken Christmas   9 Marco Discendenti Holy Crap!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>