<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>singles on Red Ambassador Music</title><link>https://redambassadormusic.com/categories/singles/</link><description>Recent content in singles on Red Ambassador Music</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://redambassadormusic.com/categories/singles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dusk</title><link>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/dusk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/dusk/</guid><description>Close your eyes, sit back, and feel the stillness sweep over you. Quiet synths introduce you to a calm and peaceful realm where the world seems right and clear. Then soft guitars take you airborne and show a view of the world from overhead as the sun sets in the distance. This is Dusk.
I am very excited to share with you my new song which I’m calling “Dusk.” I had shared a WIP with you all on Soundcloud for a while under the working title of “Morning Coffee.</description></item><item><title>Time</title><link>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/time/</guid><description>Time has a very unique sound. It&amp;rsquo;s probably best described as an electronic / steam-punk track.
Time starts out very soft and innocent, with sounds of industry (trains and machine squeaks) in the background. The chorus gets hard and heavy, grinding out the melody. The second and third choruses, the lead comes in, releasing rich melodies to complete the whole theme.
You can listen to &amp;ldquo;Time&amp;rdquo; on some common platforms linked below, or you may choose to buy the track, name your price (i.</description></item><item><title>Particulate</title><link>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/particulate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/particulate/</guid><description>I released my song “Particulate” a couple days ago. I started out by just posting a screen-recording video of the song on YouTube and then later posted it on SoundCloud.
A couple days after the SC posting, I found out that the CEDM (or Christian Electronic Dance Music) network re-posted my song to their Soundcloud profile, which was super cool! I feel pretty honored to have gotten that recognition.</description></item><item><title>Lost</title><link>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/lost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redambassadormusic.com/blog/lost/</guid><description>This is a brand new song I wrote rather quickly. I haven’t written an original song in a long while. I’ve been doing remixes and whatnot. I had a lot of fun making this and got really passionate about it.
In this song, I kind of went back to my deeper, serious, and more thoughtful side. It’s quieter. It’s got a nice, deep cello and some rich synths pulsating through. I also recorded a little vocal line for the chorus that adds a little more of a human element to it.</description></item></channel></rss>